[
  {
    "id": "c1",
    "title": "Software Structures and Models",
    "quizzes": [
      {
        "id": "c1a1",
        "title": "Modelling",
        "exercises": [
          {
            "id": "c1e1",
            "question": "Modelling first question",
            "answer": "Modelling first answer"
          },
          {
            "id": "c2e2",
            "question": "Modelling second question",
            "answer": "Modelling second answer"
          },
          {
            "id": "c3e3",
            "question": "Modelling third question",
            "answer": "Modelling third answer"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": "c1a2",
        "title": "Algorithms",
        "exercises": [
          {
            "id": "c1e3",
            "question": "Algorithms question 1",
            "answer": "Algorithms answer 1"
          },
          {
            "id": "c1e4",
            "question": "Algorithms question 2",
            "answer": "Algorithms answer 2"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "c2",
    "title": "Finnish For Foreigners 3",
    "quizzes": [
      {
        "id": "c2a1",
        "title": "Finnish",
        "exercises": [
          {
            "id": "c1e3",
            "question": "Finnish question 1",
            "answer": "Finnish answer 1"
          },
          {
            "id": "c1e4",
            "question": "Finnish question 2",
            "answer": "Finnish answer 2"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "c3",
    "title": "Application Development Methods",
    "quizzes": [
      {
        "id": "c3a1",
        "title": "Mathematics",
        "exercises": [
          {
            "id": "c1e3",
            "question": "ADM question 1",
            "answer": "ADM answer 1"
          },
          {
            "id": "c1e4",
            "question": "ADM question 2",
            "answer": "ADM answer 2"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": "c3a2",
        "title": "Java Programming",
        "exercises": [
          {
          "id": "c1e3",
          "question": "Java programming question 1",
          "answer": "Java programming answer 1"
        },
        {
          "id": "c1e4",
          "question": "Java programming question 2",
          "answer": "Java programming answer 2"
        }
      ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "c4",
    "title": "Web Programming",
    "quizzes": [
      {
        "id": "c3a1",
        "title": "Databases",
        "exercises": [
          {
            "id": "c1e3",
            "question": "Databases question 1",
            "answer": "Algorithms answer 1"
          },
          {
            "id": "c1e4",
            "question": "Databases question 2",
            "answer": "Algorithms answer 2"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": "c3a2",
        "title": "English",
        "exercises": [
          {
          "id": "c1e3",
          "question": "English question 1",
          "answer": "Algorithms answer 1"
        },
        {
          "id": "c1e4",
          "question": "English question 2",
          "answer": "Algorithms answer 2"
        }
      ]
      }
    ]
  }
]
